[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Say Anything, Lloyds nickname for his nephew is Little J.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A new- and altogether different- screen excitement!!! is the tag line from which movie?", "correct_answer": "Psycho", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas Chainsaw Massacre", "The Exorcist", "Omen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Farfalle is a French word meaning butterfly.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed occurred in Thailand, has very slim elongated body, short fur and very large ears.", "correct_answer": "Oriental Shorthair", "incorrect_answers": ["Selkirk Rex", "Singapura", "Siamese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vietnamese-born French film director, Anh Hung Tran, directed this great movie in 1993.", "correct_answer": "The Scent of Green Papaya", "incorrect_answers": ["Freedom of the Forest", "The Day of Wild Orchids", "The Day of Ho Chi Minh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the Amish Bowler in Kingpin that Roy recruited to play in the Reno Open?", "correct_answer": "Ishmael Boorg", "incorrect_answers": ["Hiram Miller", "Max Yoder", "Jonas Salk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Shaolin temples are perhaps the Buddhist monasteries best known in the West. The word Shaolin means this.", "correct_answer": "Young Forest", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue Sky", "Silent Soul", "Pure Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress was honored with a Razzie Award for Worst Actress for her role in the 1982 film Butterfly?", "correct_answer": "Pia Zadora", "incorrect_answers": ["Olivia Newton-John", "Shelley Duvall", "Nancy Allen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the Hockey Hall of Fame located?", "correct_answer": "Toronto, Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["Colorado Springs, Colorado", "Goshen, New York", "Oklahoma City, Oklahoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the movie in which Marilyn Monroe famously sings the song Diamonds Are a Girls Best Friend?", "correct_answer": "Gentlemen Prefer Blondes", "incorrect_answers": ["The Prince and the Showgirl", "Some Like It Hot", "How to Marry a Millionaire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Japanese folklore, this kind of fox is unusual and has special abilities.", "correct_answer": "Kitsune", "incorrect_answers": ["Nuckalavee", "Gamera", "Ghidorah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pamela Lillian Isley is Poisin Ivy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]